

Mugia Miftahul Choir

Nationality: Indonesian (+62) 83816355113 **Date of birth:** 18/06/2001

Gender: Male **Email address:** <u>mugia.miftahul@gmail.com</u>

Website: https://mugia.herokuapp.com/

Website: https://www.artstation.com/mugiamiftahulchoir8

Whatsapp Messenger: +62 83816355113

in LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/mugia-choir-3b593a1b4/

O Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/mugiadesign/

• Address: Cicadas, Sagalaherang, Subang, Jawa Barat, Indonesia, 41282 Subang (Ind

onesia)

ABOUT ME

I'm a university student at Universitas Komputer Indonesia majoring in information systems. I have an interest in 3D art and Web Development. I've gained experience working on a different scale of projects, from individual projects to corporate class projects. Yet I still have great determination in learning new stuff. I also have experience of working with people from different countries and cultures such, so I can communicate well with others and am capable of working alone or inside a team.

WORK EXPERIENCE

3D artist

RFIDiom Ltd [03/09/2021 - 10/02/2022]

City: Liverpool

Country: United Kingdom

I was a part of the Marketing Team at RFIDiom Ltd; my main activities were creating graphics content for social media, or blog. But I also contributed to Branding a few of the company's products. And designing UI/UX of a product website.

My special responsibilities were to create 3D assets and create 3D animations; usually, they were used to demo or advertise products.

On occasions I was also responsible for quality assurance on some websites, looking for errors, bugs, etc.

3D artist

WakafPro Multimedia Internasional [11/07/2022 – 26/08/2022]

City: Bandung **Country:** Indonesia

I officially worked at WakafPro for 7 weeks but got an additional 1-week assignment that was not related to 3D modeling. I was assigned to the production team. The task is to create 3D assets that are used for company product content, as well as for virtual reality projects. My work includes 3D modeling and texturing

Web developer

MTs Al-Hidayah Sagalaherang [06/2020 – 02/2021]

City: Subang

Country: Indonesia

I held all of the jobs in the web development process by myself, including:

doing a brief with the client, sketching, wireframing, prototyping, creating high fidelity UI design, designing and implementing a database, front-end, and back-end job

Web developer

SMAN 1 Jalancagak Scout Organization [04/2020 - 06/2021]

City: Subang

Country: Indonesia

My responsibilities were designing the UI of the website, developing the website according to the design, designing and implementing a database, giving the required training for the users, and maintaining the website after it was online

Graphic designer

Mamah Coet Restaurant [29/11/2020]

City: Subang

Country: Indonesia

They came to me to create a simpler version of their logo for some urgent business, so I only have a day to finish the job. What I did was taking a few hours of brainstorming to simplify their logo, aligning my idea with the client, creating a prototype and handing it to them, then doing some revisions

Graphic designer

Mamah Coet Restaurant [02/11/2019 - 03/11/2019]

City: Subang

Country: Indonesia

I was only tasked to design a banner for their new opening restaurant, so i started by collecting the assets, choosing the art direction, fonts style, and colors because they didn't have an established brand style to follow yet

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Digital Marketing and Graphic Design Training

PT Inovasi Telematika Nusantara [30/06/2021 – 03/07/2021]

VirtualTraining.id

Web & Mobille Design Training

Zero to Mastery [30/12/2020 - 15/02/2021]

zerotomastery.io

React.js Training

Zero to Mastery [03/11/2020 - 27/12/2020]

zerotomastery.io

React Native Training

Zero to Mastery [04/03/2021 - 04/04/2021]

zerotomastery.io

Fundamental Front-End Web Development Training

Dicoding [10/06/2020 – 29/06/2020]

<u>dicoding.com</u>

3D Modeling Training

GameDev.tv [17/06/2021 - 08/09/2021]

gamedev.tv

3D Character Creator for Video Games Training

GameDev.tv [14/09/2021 - 27/09/2021]

gamedev.tv

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Indonesian

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING C1 READING B2 WRITING B2

SPOKEN PRODUCTION B2 SPOKEN INTERACTION B2

DIGITAL SKILLS

My Digital Skills

Design

Adobe Photoshop / Corel Draw / React - React Native / Adobe Illustrator / Figma

Office

Microsoft Excel / Microsoft Office / Microsoft Powerpoint

Programming

React ecosystem: ReactJS, React Router, Redux, Typescript / HTML5/CSS3, SASS, JavaScript (including recent versions) / PHP Laravel / Javascript ECMA6

3D

Blender, 3D modeling / 3D animation